Let's unbox one of the most hyped date
night scent for men. Super excited.
So, this is Stronger with You by Emporio
Armani and everyone is talking about
this. Finally, I got my hands on this
beauty. Wo! Just look at the bottle
here.
Wow. This bottle is sleek, classy, and
very minimal. Okay, so this opens up
sweet, warm, and spicy. I'm getting that
vanilla, chestnut, and to be honest,
it's a bit on a sweeter yet spicy style.
Top notes are chestnut and sugar. And
when it settles down, you'll smell
sugar, vanilla, lavender. You will
genuinely feel rich and premium if you
wear this. So, this is priced at 6,600
rupees INR. And I'm sure if you buy
online or look from other websites,
you'll get at least a 10% discount on
this one. Longevity is easily around 6
to 8 hours. And I'm saying this because
I've already used Armani perfume. This
is a compliment magnet for sure. Worth
adding this to your collection.